

Arthur Baudel

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Details

Nationality: French
Phone number: + 33 7 66 54 14 95
E-mail: arthur.baudel@yahoo.fr
Github: github.com/arthurcommit
Portfolio: arthurcommit.github.io/

Skills

- Create custom websites, themes and plugins in WordPress
 - Transpose the graphic models into web language in the CMS
 - Maintenance and bug fixes
 - Adaptability, ability to work on various subjects
 - Team player

Technology Stack

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, WordPress, WooCommerce PHP, Javascript, MVC, SQL, Git and Github

Profile

I am a positive driven and confident individual with an apt for learning new technology. I enjoy problem-solving and coding. Always strive to bring 100% to the work I do. Bringing 2 years web development experience. I have worked on technologies like HTML,CSSS3, JavaScript, WordPress, PHP during my Bachelor's.

Work experiences

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER APPRENTICESHIP - UBALLERS (PARIS)

OCTOBER 2021 - MARCH 2022

- Front-end and back-end development using HTML, CSS, Javascript and jQuery, PHP.
- Improving design of the website: user interface (UI) and user experience (UX).
- Implementing enhancements that improved web functionality and responsiveness.
- Testing websites and performed user testing before the website goes live.
- Writing of technical notices

WAITER - THE LITTLE FRENCH DELI (MELBOURNE - AUSTRALIA)

APRIL 2019 - APRIL 2021

Education

3W ACADEMY (PARIS - FRANCE)

MAY 2021 - MARCH 2022 Web and mobile web developer

Courseworks: Website design, User Experience, Front-end and Back-end Development, Database Administration, App Programming.

UDEMY

Online WordPress Course:

- Creation of a business website
- Creation of an e-commerce site
- Optimization of a Wordpress website